 questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "It is a widely used programming language that enables interactive and dynamic content on websites.",
        answer: "D.	JavaScript",
        options: [
            "A. HTML",
            "B.	Python",
            "C.	C++",
            "D.	JavaScript",  
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "JavaScript was created by ________ in 1995?",
        answer: "B. Brendan Eich",
        options: [
           "A. James Gosling",
           "B. Brendan Eich",
           "C. Dennis Ritchie",
           "D. Guido van Rossum",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What are the types of values that can be represented and manipulated in a programming language?",
        answer: "A. Data Types",
        options: [
            "A. Data Types",
            "B. Variables",
            "C. Operators",
            "D. Functions",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "These are the building blocks of any programming language.",
        answer: "B. Variables",
        options: [
            "A. Data Types",
            "B. Variables",
            "C. Operators",
            "D. Functions",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "If three constants x, y, and z are declared and initialized with the values 5, 6, and the sum of x and y respectively, and then a message is logged to the console using console.log with the text 'The total is:' followed by the value of z, what will be the output displayed in the console when this JavaScript code is executed? ",
        answer: "C. 11",
        options: [
            "A. 15",
            "B. 10",
            "C. 11",
            "D. 13",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How many choices are possible when using a single if-else statement? ",
        answer: "B. 2",
        options: [
            "A. 1",
            "B. 2",
            "C. 3",
            "D. 4",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What do you use in programming when you want to do the same task over and over again?  ",
        answer: "C. Loops",
        options: [
            "A. Conditional",
            "B. Functions",
            "C. Loops",
            "D. Variables",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "If the variable i is initially set to 3 and the following loop is executed: while (i < 15), where within the loop i is printed, followed by a line break, and i is then multiplied by 3. What sequence of numbers would be displayed as a result of running this code?  ",
        answer: "A. 3, 6, 9, 12, 15 ",
        options: [
            "A. 3, 6, 9, 12, 15 ",
            "B. 3, 9 ",
            "C. 3, 6, 12 ",
            "D. 3, 9, 15 ",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What programming feature lets you group a series of task under a single name, making it easy to reuse throughout your code by invoking that name?",
        answer: "B. Functions",
        options: [
            "A. Conditional",
            "B. Functions",
            "C. Loops",
            "D. Variables",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "If a JavaScript function named greet is defined to take a parameter called name and, when called with the argument 'Bob', it executes the statement document.write('Hello, ' + name + '!');, what would be the output when the function greet is invoked with the argument 'Bob'? ",
        answer: "B. Hello, Bob!",
        options: [
            "A. Undefined",
            "B. Hello, Bob!",
            "C. greet(“Bob!”) ",
            "D. Bob ",
        ]
    }
];